Guide to the Communications Committee, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Communications Committee, Yale University Library, records
2002-2005
RU 1043
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
The records consist of minutes, correspondence, reports, and bulletins documenting the mission and activities of the Yale University Library Communications Committee.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-E (YRG 32-E), Records of Yale University Library programs, projects, and committees.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the chair of the Communications Committee, 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Biographical / Historical
The Communications Committee of the Yale University Library was formed in 2003 by the Library Management Council and the Microcosm Group. Its charge and mission is to support and promote an environment of two way communication by recommending, advising on and facilitating the exchange of ideas, the availability of information, and the use of good communication methods and skills.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, correspondence, reports, and bulletins documenting the mission and activities of the Yale University Library Communications Committee.
Academic libraries; Communication in management; Yale University. Library
- Communications Committee records, 2002-2005; Accession 2007-A-175
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2041
  - Mission and charge, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 4)
  - Goals, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee subgroups, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Products and reports, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Guidelines for Committee Participation" (brochure), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - High Performing Organizations (HPO) survey results, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Focus group results, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 12)